Stereographic Cards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Verso: Mighty El Capitan, Yosemite, California: Dominatng the entrance of Yosemite, El Capitan lifs its high walls 3,604 feet above the quiet-flowing, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 77-verso (Box 1604)
  - Eloquent Testimonoy to Zeal of Early Spanish Missionaries-Mission of San Juan Capistrano, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Mission San Juan Capistrano, California: Here in the Mission patio is a statue of Father Junipero Serra, beloved founder of the mission., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 78-verso (Box 1604)
  - One of the Finest Municipal Buildings in the World-City Hall, Los Angeles, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Los Angeles City Hall, Los Angeles, California: From 1781, the time of settlement by Spanish people for the purpose of raising foodstuffs, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 79-verso (Box 1604)
  - Home of Two of America's Best Love Film Artists, Beverly Hills, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: "Pickfair," The Charming Pickford-Fairbanks Home, Beverly Hills, Calif.: Between Los Angeles and the ocean, on a hilltop of Beverly Hills, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 80-verso (Box 1604)
  - Rookery of Sea Lions, Santa Barbara Islands, off Coast of California., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Sea Lions at the Santa Barbara Islands, California: This rocky and desolate shore lies on San Miguel Island, the westernmost bit of land, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 81-verso (Box 1604)
  - Looking N:E: from Twin Peaks down Market St. to Ferry Building, San Francisco, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Market Street and the Bay from Twin Peaks, San Francisco, Calif.: You are looking down Market Street, the chief business street of San Francisco., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 82-verso (Box 1604)
  - Remarkable Earthquake Fissure in the Sobrante Hills, near Berkeley, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Earthquake Fissure near Berkely, California: Berkeley is on the east shore of San Francisco bay 10 miles northeast of San Francisco. This view, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 83-verso (Box 1604)
  - Harvesting Almonds, San Joaquin Co., Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Harvesting Almonds, California: Practically all our almonds come from Spain, Italy and France. But there are sections of our country so like, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 84-verso (Box 1604)
  - Band Saw Cutting Redwood Log, Calif., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Band Saw Cutting Redwood Log, California: This enormous log was once the trunk of a stately tree such as you can see in view No. 229., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 85-verso (Box 1604)
  - Mt. Shasta (14440 Ft.) North over Strawberry Valley and Sisson, California., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Mount Shasta Monarch of the Cascade Range, California: The mighty bulwark of Mount Shasta gains much of its majesty not alone from its, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 86-verso (Box 1604)
  - A Lake with a Wondrous Story-Crater Lake, Oregon., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Crater Lake, Oregon: Thousands of years ago there stood, where this conical island now rises, a mountain to which the name Mount Mazoma, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 87-verso (Box 1604)
  - Hydraulic Mining, Ore., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Hydraulic Mining, Oregon: In certain parts of our country, and in other countries, gold has been found mixed with sand and gravel., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 88-verso (Box 1604)
  - Majestic Mount Hood Rising 12,000 Feet in Solitary Splendor, Oregon., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Majestic Mount Hood Rising 12,000 Feet in Solitary Splendor, Oregon: Behold Mount Hood, the pride of Oregon! It is in the northwestern, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 89-verso (Box 1604)
  - Picturesque Grandeur of Columbia River, West Past :"Pillars of Hercules," Oregon, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Columbia River, West Past "Pillars of Hercules," Oregon: You are looking down the river toward Portland and the Pacific Ocean fifty miles, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 90-verso (Box 1604)
  - The Silvery Spray of Multnomah Falls, Columbia River, Oregon., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Silvery Spray of Multnomah Falls, Columbia River, Oregon: When a main river valley is greatly deepened, it often happens that the valleys, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 91-verso (Box 1604)
  - Cleaning Salmon-Interior of a Canning Establishment, Astoria, Ore., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Butchering Salmon Canning Factory, Astoria, Oregon: One of the easiest ways of catching salmon is by a fish wheel fastened to a boat., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 92-verso (Box 1604)
  - Great Chained Log Rafts on the Columbia River, Wash., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Rafts of Logs, Columbia River, Washington: One of the greatest lumbering districts in the United States is in the extreme northwestern part., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 93-verso (Box 1604)
  - Mt. Rainier from Mirror Lake, Indian Henry's Hunting Ground, Mt. Rainier National Park, Washington., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Mount Rainier Reflected in Mirror Lake, Washington: In 1899, a National park 324 square miles in area was created to contain Mount Rainier, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 94-verso (Box 1604)
  - View N. from Smith Bldg. over Some of Seattle's Finest Business Buildings, Wash., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: A Wonder City of the Pacific Northwest-Seattle, Wash.: Seattle, the seaboard metropolis of the state of Washington, is one of the outstanding, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 95-verso (Box 1604)
  - Loading Lumber on Ships, Wash., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Shipping Lumber, Washington: Here you are directly back of the greatest lumber mill in the world. This is at Port Blakely, near Seattle, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 96-verso (Box 1604)
  - In the Land of the Totem Poles-the Indian Village of Kasaan, Alaska., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Totem Poles and Indian Village of Kasaan, Alaska: Kasaan, ("Pretty Town," in the Tlingit dialect) is one of three villages on Prince of Wales Island, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 97-verso (Box 1604)
  - Drying Fish on the Yukon River, Alaska., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Drying Fish, Yukon River, Alaska: This view shows a group fo natives on the banks of the Yukon. The Yukon flows through the central part of, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 98-verso (Box 1604)
  - Transportation over Icy Trails North of the Arctic Circle, Alaska., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Over Icy Trails North of Arctic Circle, Alaska: Arctic City is near the Arctic Circle on a branch of the Yukon River. You would know by everything, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 99-verso (Box 1604)
  - Moraine Lake and Valley of the Ten Peaks, Canadian Rockies, B. C., Canada, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100 (Box 1604)
  - Verso: Moraine Lake and Valley of the Ten Peaks, Canadian Rockies, B. C., Canada: Walter Dwight Wilcox, who name Moraine Lake, says of this scene, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 100-verso (Box 1604)
  Box 1605
- Stereographic Cards, 2.1.8
  - Summer Crowds at America's Foremost Seaside Resort, Atlantic City, New Jersey, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Summer Crowds at America's Foremost Seaside Resort, Atlantic City, New Jersey: Atlantic City lives on the beach, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 1-verso (Box 1605)
  - See them from the Air! - The World Renowned Skyscrapers of Lower New York City, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: See them from the Air! - The World Renowned Skyscrapers of Lower New York City: What tremendous power is concentrated in this little area!..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 2-verso (Box 1605)
  - Statue of Liberty, Bedloe's Island, New York Harbor, N.Y., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Statue of Liberty, Bedloe's Island, New York Harbor, N.Y.: Some years before the United States celebrated the 100th anniversary of the Declaration of Independence, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 3-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Leviathan, originally the Vaterland - a Palatial Ocean Liner with a Notable War and Peace record, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Leviathan, originally the Vaterland - a Palatial Ocean Liner with a Notable War and Pleace record: To millions of Americans the name of the Leviathan is intimately associated with our efforts in the World War..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 4-verso (Box 1605)
  - Bathers at Coney Island, New York's most popular beach resort, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: bathers at Coney Island, New York's most popular beach resort: This is New York's oldest, most crowded and most spectacular beach resort and outdoor amusement center, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 5-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Great White Way - Night Scene on Broadway Above Times Square, New York City, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Great White Way - Night Scene on Broadway Above Times Square, New York City: The blazing illumination occasioned by millions of electric lights, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 6-verso (Box 1605)
  - From Empire Building, looking North on Broadway past Trinity Church, New York City, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: From Empire Building, looking North on Broadway past Trinity Church, New York City: What would be the feelings of doughty old Peter Minuit, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 7-verso (Box 1605)
  - "The Cathedral of Commerce" - Woolworth Building, product of Five and Ten Cent Pieces, New York City, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: "The Cathedral of Commerce" - Woolworth Building, product of Five and Ten Cent Pieces, New York City: Dr. S. Parkes Cadman, the noted divine, has called this building "The Cathedral of Commerce," a term which fittingly describes it., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 8-verso (Box 1605)
  - New York City's proudest thoroughfare - Fifth Avenue looking North from Thirty-eighth street, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: New York City's proudest thoroughfare - Fifth Avenue looking North from Thirty-eighth street: Fifth Avenue is one of the mostn famous streets in the world, a center of business, fashion and wealth, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 9-verso (Box 1605)
  - "The Forest of Manhattan" - skyscrapers of Lower New York, seen over the city of Brooklyn, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: "The forest of Manhattan" - skyscrapers of Lower New York, seen over the city of Brooklyn: From whatever direction seen - up the bay from Staten Island or Governor's Island, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 10-verso (Box 1605)
  - Boxing Grapefruit in Modern Plant, Fla., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Boxing Grapefruit in Modern Plant, Fla.: Grapefruit grows on trees from twenty to thirty feet high, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 11-verso (Box 1605)
  - Harvesting Indian River Pineapples, a Native American fruit, in Florida, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Harvesting Indian River Pineapples, a Native American fruit, in Florida: The pineapple (Annas Sativus) is a native of the American tropics, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 12-verso (Box 1605)
  - Chipping Virgin Turpentine Trees, Ga., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Chipping Virgin Turpentine Trees, Ga.: Turpentine, tar, pitch and rosin are made from the sap of the long-leaf pine., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 13-verso (Box 1605)
  - A beautiful scene in Magnolia Gardens, near Charleston, South Carolina, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: A beautiful scene in Magnolia Gardens, near Charleston, South Carolina: These lovely gardens on the Ashley River, twelve miles from the city, seem to be a scene from fairyland, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 14-verso (Box 1605)
  - Distilling Turpentine from the Crude Resin - in the Pine Forest of North Carolina., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Distilling turpentine from the crude resin - in the pine forest of North Carolina: Turpentine is a resinous juice called oleoresin, extracted from several species of coniferous trees..., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 15-verso (Box 1605)
  - One of nature's curiosities, the Natural Bridge in Virginia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: One of nature's curiosities, the Natural Bridge in Virginia: We are now in the heart of the Blue Ridge country, one of the most beautiful parts of Virginia, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 16-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Singing Tower, "The Taj Mahal of America," Mountain Lake, Florida, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The singing Tower, "The Taj Mahal of America," Mountain Lake, Florida: One of the latest and most beautiful creations of American architecture here stands before us, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 17-verso (Box 1605)
  - Luxuriant Tropical Verdure on the Anclote River, Florida, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Luxuriant Tropical Verdure on the Anclote River, Florida: "The Everglade State," as Florida is often called, has had a checkered but always romantic history, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 18-verso (Box 1605)
  - Shelter and cultivation of High Grade cigar tobacco, Alabama, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Shelter and cultivation of High Grade cigar tobacco, Alabama: All over the world today a great number of institutions and other agencies are engaged in the scientific study of problems of agriculture, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 19-verso (Box 1605)
  - Picking cotton on a Mississippi Plantation, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Picking cotton on a Mississippi Plantation: This is what harvesting means in the South, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 20-verso (Box 1605)
  - Inspecting plate glass after polishing, Rossford, Ohio, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Inspecting plate glass after polishing, Rossford, Ohio: After the plate glass has been rolled and properly cooled (annealed) it is taken to a cutting room where it is shaped to the proper size, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 21-verso (Box 1605)
  - Method of placing material in furnace - Plate Glass Works, Rossford, O., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Method of placing material in furnace - Plate Glass Works, Rossford, O.: Plate glass is made of pure sand, carbonate of lime, sulphate of soda, and carbon in the form of coke and coal, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 22-verso (Box 1605)
  - United States Air Mail plane at Cleveland, Ohio., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: United States Air Mail plane at Cleveland, Ohio.: "Air Mail" is the latest and fastest mail service furnished by the United States Post Office Department, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 23-verso (Box 1605)
  - Traffic in the Public Square and Euclid Avenue, Cleveland, Ohio, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Traffic in the Public Square and Euclid Avenue, Cleveland, Ohio: We are in the very heart of Cleveland, county seat of Cuyahoga County, and fifth city in size in the United States, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 24-verso (Box 1605)
  - Taking Automobile Tires from the Curing Pits. Akron, Ohio, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Taking Automobile Tires from the Curing Pits. Akron, Ohio: In this view the tires have just gone through the "curing" process, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 25-verso (Box 1605)
  - "All Aboard!" giant plane at Columbus, O., on first Air-Rail trip, New York to Los Angeles, July 2, 1929., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: "All Aboard!" giant plane at Columbus, O., on first Air-Rail trip, New York to Los Angeles, July 2, 1929.: In 1869 the people of the United States rejoiced in the completion of the Union Pacific Railroad, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 26-verso (Box 1605)
  - Corrugating and washing rubber just received from the Plantation. Akron, Ohio, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Corrugating and washing rubber just received from the Plantation. Akron, Ohio: This picture was taken in a great rubber goods factory in Akron, Ohio., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 27-verso (Box 1605)
  - Hanging tobacco in shed for curing. Lexington, Ky, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Hanging tobacco in shed for curing. Lexington, Ky: Young tobacco plants are grown from seeds in hothouses or under glass frames set to catch the sunlight, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 28-verso (Box 1605)
  - The birthplace of Abraham Lincoln, Hodgenville, Kentucky, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The birthplace of Abraham Lincoln, Hodgenville, Kentucky: There is no figure in the history of our country that has a greater inspirational value for us than Lincoln, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 29-verso (Box 1605)
  - Chattanooga and Tennessee River Valley from Lookout Mountain, Tennessee, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Chattanooga and Tennessee River Valley from Lookout Mountain, Tennessee: This view from Lookout Mountain is most wonderful, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 30-verso (Box 1605)
  - When King Carnival reigns in the New Orleans Mardi Gras, La., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: When King Carnival reigns in the New Orleans Mardi Gras, La.: Ever since its founding in 1718 by the Sieur de Bienville, New Orleans has been a place of romance, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 31-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Great Wilson Dam at Muscle Shoals, Alabama, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Great Wilson Dam at Muscle Shoals, Alabama: The huge structure before us is the greatest concrete dam in the world., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 32-verso (Box 1605)
  - A Nation's shrine - home of Washington, founder of the republic, Mount Vernon, Va., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: A Nation's shrine - home of Washington, founder of the republic, Mount Vernon, Va.: This is in Fairfax County, Virginia, on the right bank of the Potomac, ten miles below Washington, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 33-verso (Box 1605)
  - Home of Thomas Jefferson, Monticello, Va., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Home of Thomas Jefferson, Monticello, Va.: Located in Albemarle County, under the shadow of the Blue Ridge, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 34-verso (Box 1605)
  - A startling privilege of the age - seeing the World Metropolis from an airplane, New York City, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: A startling privilege of the age - seeing the World Metropolis from an airplane, New York City: We are looking north over Manhattan Island, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 35-verso (Box 1605)
  - Capitol of the Old Dominion, once capital of the Confederate States, Richmond, Va., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Capitol of the Old Dominion, once capital of the Confederate States, Richmond, Va.: It was Thomas Jefferson who, while minister to France, conceived the idea of modeling the Virginia capitol, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 36-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Old Colonial Church, restored, Jamestown, Va., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Old Colonial Church, restored, Jamestown, Va.: On the low, unhealthful land surrounding this vine-clad church was enacted the romantic and often tragic drama, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 37-verso (Box 1605)
  - Huge pile of Oyster Shells to be used as "bedding" of young oysters. Hampton, Va., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Huge pile of Oyster Shells to be used as "bedding" of young oysters. Hampton, Va.: Millions of oysters are caught in the waters along the shores of the Middle Atlantic States and of the southern New England states, each fall and winter, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 38-verso (Box 1605)
  - Spraying with Arsenate of lead, Truck Gardens, near Norfolk, Va., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Spraying with Arsenate of lead, Truck Gardens, near Norfolk, Va.: In crowded cities few people have the space to raise their own vegetables, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 39-verso (Box 1605)
  - The Rocky Coast of Maine - Cape Neddick Light, York Nubble, Me., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The Rocky Coast of Maine - Cape Neddick Light, York Nubble, Me.: The state of Maine has so many deep, fiord-like harbors, which are well protected from storms, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 40-verso (Box 1605)
  - Logs from the forest delivered at the stream, Aroostook County, Me., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Logs from the forest delivered at the stream, Aroostook County, Me.: Lumbering is an important industry in northern Maine where this picture was taken, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 41-verso (Box 1605)
  - Charming outlook across valley to the White Mountains - Mt. Washington in distance, New Hampshire, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Charming outlook across valley to the White Mountains - Mt. Washington in distance, New Hampshire: The summit of Mount Washington is the highest point in the United States east of the rockies and the north of North Carolina, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 42-verso (Box 1605)
  - Marble Quarry in Vermont, near Proctor - largest single quarry opening, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Marble Quarry in Vermont, near Proctor - largest single quarry opening: Although Vermont, "the Green Mountain State," ranks only forty-second among the states of the Union in area, and forty-fifth in population, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 43-verso (Box 1605)
  - Quarrying granite, Concord, N.H., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Quarrying granite, Concord, N.H.: Granite is quarried, which means that it is taken out of an open shaft, or pit, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 44-verso (Box 1605)
  - The birthplace of Horace Greeley, near Amherst, N.H., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: The birthplace of Horace Greeley, near Amherst, N.H.: To the generation of Americans living in the last two decades preceeding the outbreak of the Civil War, the figure of Horace Greeley, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 45-verso (Box 1605)
  - Picturesque New England - Otter Creek, Near Rutland, Vermont, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Picturesque New England - Otter Creek, Near Rutland, Vermont: Vermont, "the Green Mountain state," long ago gained its popular name from its picturesque ranges of mountains, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 46-verso (Box 1605)
  - Llana Cascades, Lake Dunmore, Vermont, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Llana Cascades, Lake Dunmore, Vermont: Deeply hidden among the ridges of the Red Sandrock Mountains, sloping westward from the Green Mountains toward Lake Champlain, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 47-verso (Box 1605)
  - General view in large printing room of Cotton Mills, Lawrence, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: General view in large printing room of Cotton Mills, Lawrence, Mass.: The gray cotton cloth that comes from the loom is singed over a gas flame to make it smooth, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 48-verso (Box 1605)
  - Spinning cotton yarn in the Great Textile Mills, Lawrence, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49 (Box 1605)
  - Verso: Spinning cotton yarn in the Great Textile Mills, Lawrence, Mass.: When one looks at a view of this sort, he is confused by the great number of machines, circa late 1920s - 1930s; 49-verso (Box 1605)
  - Where the Revolutionary War began, April 19, 1775 - the town common, Lexington, Mass., circa late 1920s - 1930s; 50 (Box 1605)